Then fix up a romantic date and give a foot massage.
They'll provide a sleeping aid to all shift workers.
I'd like two eggs, avocado, an English muffin, and fresh Pico de Gallo if available.
Starbucks is very interesting and fun to me.
Mixed lamb and chicken over rice with chopped pita is my dream come true.
A headshot is needed to proc the DoT.
Tying a guy down via a baby is a really, really bad idea.
I'm on day three of my Assassin's Creed marathon.
Three billion an hour solo makes me a poor noob.
There's a whacky waving inflatable tube man by the road.
Drunk me is a genius until sober me realizes what a horrible idea the night before was.
Everyone is beautiful regardless of color, size, race, gender, or orientation.
This guy helped make adult cartoons like Steve Jobs helped computer technology.
Sorry, Iron Banner is causing a sodium overflow.
Abandon all hope, you who try to destroy my Tombstone.
I overcame a challenge and got fifty challenges as a reward.
It's already made, already released, already universally panned, and already barely making back its budget.
Yes, I'm working out after a ten hour workday.
I've been accpted to Virginia Tech and Georgia Tech, both with partial academic scholarships.
Well, America did drop two massive amounts of freedom on Japan.
Nine days into the month, the number of homicides in Chicago nearly equals the number in all of last February.
Please welcome a chattering skeleton on loan from Disneyland, Larry King.
I predict Wales and Australia will go through an absolute shocked result.
See, I took the easy way out and took blow-off classes.
I peed my pants during my sophomore year in high school.
I am pretty honest and I am sitting patiently right here.
Rest seems fine for a high ammo map like payload maps.
Just come to my yard. I'll make you swallow raw fish.
You'll look gorgeous no matter what.
There's a positive regression to rushing TDs and a negative regression to thrown TDs.
Glasses break at parties too easily so we use Solo cups in Canada too.
I grew up in Chipley. I am originally from Fort Walton Beach, where my tornado story comes from.
Try this: right click, save target as, and save to desktop.
I'm searching desperately for a Mega Man amiibo in SoCal, specifically the Coachella Valley.
Warriors GM Bob Myers says the team has reached out to Ray Allen's representatives.
Warning: Fake game key requests have been floating around recently Here are some tips on how to avoid them.
Oklahoma loses to TCU, who loses to Oklahoma State, who loses to Oklahoma.
Fine, I'll see you soon.
That has longer range, higher speed, and higher capacity than similarly-sized traditional rotorcraft.
For example, sixteen is the age of consent in Ohio.
Well I have to go offline now. Have a nice day ahead!
Drink scotch whiskey all night long and die behind the wheel.
I like anime, video games, adventuring, trying new things, and chilling.
Copy the headline, paste it into Google, and click the WSJ link.
Praying is wholly spiritual giving, so nothing is returned.
I'm from Columbus, my college town was Columbus, and I live in Columbus now. It's rather similar.
I like comics, games, books, news, music, television, shopping, and general Internet browsing.
I have a diagnosed disorder of the obsessive-compulsive variety.
Tim Cook approved an Apple electric car project a year ago; hundreds of employees are working on it.
I'm so sorry. I followed you again.
If their own way is oppressive or ignores privilege, I'd say the others would be right.
I appreciate the effort to help the geographically challenged.
We'll do it ourselves.
Last year I lived in LA, Las Vegas, Colorado, Madison, and Chicago.
Get your weak self a real life.
I challenge you to a car race! I'll probably drive off a cliff.
The Photoshop IB vendor area should include a salad bar.
I'm a dude, though, so I guess there's nothing surprising there.
I believe an average plasma has around two frames of input lag.
Three hours after I showered, ate, and put on pajamas, I thought: I should've put on real clothes.