I walk these streets, searching to find the steps that we left behind, Your lonely eyes stare back at mine in pictures from that time, I hold my heart, closing my eyes I see your smile, lies behind in this place,you entered my life, How I wish you were still mine I know that if I see you again, Beside that cafe we met, I'd forget about the past Lose track of time with you Talking about our lives to show you a whole new side of me And see the changes we've made, can we Be more than we have been, Start our story again All I can say, is tell you just one thing, I walk these streets, searching to find the steps that we left behind, Your lonely eyes stare back at mine in pictures from that time. 


